torrentbar.com 2013-12-26

# privacy policy at TorrentBar - www.torrentbar.com

#### Overall privacy statement

We have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you, the users of the services of TorrentBar.com and its products, how we use and protect the personal information when you use the services.

#### 1\. What information does TorrentBar collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. You are required to provide us with some information as a condition of usage during the registration. But your personally identifiable information can NOT be distinguished. What we need is only your email address which tells nothing about whom you are. Also, we may need your help by submitting information like your age, occupation, region, gender, country and so on to form the aggregate usage of TorrentBar. We do not record this as a single user's information and do not bind this information with your username or email address.

#### 2.How does TorrentBAr share the information?

We know your personal information is very important to you and us, so we will never give this information to any others.

#### 3\. Your choices

a. By using the services offered by TorrentBar, you acknowledge you agree with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Policy, you may not access or use the services of this site. You will not be notified if this policy is materially changed, you have to check this page for the latest privacy policy yourself.

b. You can refuse to register as a member of this site, then you do not have to show us any of your imformation.
